Guide to the Donald Kennedy, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0315
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1992-179
  - Miscellaneous Foundations, 1990; AD 12.10.4 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4)
  - Keck Fund/Trust, 1985-88; AD 12.10.4/6 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/6)
  - Ford Foundation, 1982-88; AD 12.10.4/71 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/71)
  - James Irvine Foundation, 1982-88; AD 12.10.4/103 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/103)
  - James Irvine Foundation, 1989/1990; AD 12.10.4/103 (Box 12, Folder AD 12.10.4/103)
  - Mellow Foundation, 1982-86; AD 12.10.4/139 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.10.4/139)
  - Mellow Foundation, 1987-89; AD 12.10.4/139 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.10.4/139)
  - San Francisco Foundation, 1982-89; AD 12.10.4/192 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.10.4/192)
  - United Way, 1988-90; AD 12.10.8 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.10.8)
  - Land and Buildings, 1988-90; AD 12.14 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.14)
  - Earthquake, 1989; AD 12.14.1/2 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.14.1/2)
  - Near West Campus Project, 1988/1989; AD 12.14.7/31 (Box 13, Folder AD 12.14.7/31)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1987-90; AD 13.10.3 (Box 13, Folder AD 13.10.3)
  - Provost's Office, 1983-87; AA 1 (Box 14, Folder AA 1)
  - Academic Computing and Info. Systems, 1983-86; PAA 1.4.1 (Box 14, Folder PAA 1.4.1)
  - Dean's Council Agenda, 1986/1987; PAA 1.5.1 (Box 14, Folder PAA 1.5.1)
  - Dean's Council Agenda, 1988/1989; AA 1.5.1 (Box 14, Folder AA 1.5.1)
  - Dean's Council Agenda, 1990; AA 1.5.1 (Box 14, Folder AA 1.5.1)
  - Dean's Retreat, 1983-87; AA 1.5.2 (Box 14, Folder AA 1.5.2)
  - Graduate Studies/Division, 1983-87; AA 1.13 (Box 14, Folder AA 1.13)
  - Graduate Studies/Division, 1988/1989; AA 1.13 (Box 14, Folder AA 1.13)
  - Faculty Lists/Statistical Reports, 1981-85; AA 2 (Box 14, Folder AA 2)
  - Emeriti, 1982-90; AA 2.2 (Box 15, Folder AA 2.2)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1982-87; AA 3 (Box 15, Folder AA 3)
  - Council of Admin., Deans Undergraduate Studies (CADUS), 9/1989-90; PAA 3.2 (Box 15, Folder PAA 3.2)
  - Continuing Education, 1986/1987; AA 3.6 (Box 15, Folder AA 3.6)
  - Continuing Education, 1988/1989; AA 3.6 (Box 15, Folder AA 3.6)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 9/1987-1988; AA 4.1 (Box 15, Folder AA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 1989; AA 4.1 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1)
  - School of Humanities and Sciences, 1990; AA 4.1 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1)
  - Humanities Center, 1982-1985; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.1/2)
  - Humanities Center, 1986/1987; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.1/2)
  - Humanities Center, 1988/1989; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.1/2)
  - Humanities Center, 1990; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.1/2)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Papers, 12/82-12/88; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.1/3)
  - Anthropology, 1982-1986; AA 4.1.5 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.5)
  - Anthropology, 1987-1989; AA 4.1.5 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.5)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 9/1987-1988; AA 4.1.12 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.12)
  - Department of Biological Sciences, 1989/1990; AA 4.1.12 (Box 16, Folder AA 4.1.12)
  - Chemistry, 1/1979-1985; AA 4.1.13 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.13)
  - Dept. of Commun./Knight Fellows, 1982-1986; AA 4.1.15 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.15)
  - Dept. of Commun./Knight Fellows, 1987-1990; AA 4.1.15 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.15)
  - Computer Science, 1979-1986; AA 4.1.17 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.17)
  - Economics, 1983-1988; AA 4.1.20 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.20)
  - Economic Policy Research, 1982-1987; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.20/1)
  - English Department, 1979-1988; AA 4.1.21 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.21)
  - Hopkins Marine Biology Center, 1982-1987; AA 4.1.28 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.28)
  - Athletics Department, 9/1987-8/88; AA 4.1.30 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Athletics Department, 9/1989-8/1990; AA 4.1.30 (Box 17, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Athletics Department, 9/1990-12/1990; AA 4.1.30 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.1.30)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1988; AA 4.2 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.2)
  - Graduate School of Business, 1989; AA 4.2 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.2)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 1985-1988; AA 4.3 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.3)
  - 0, 1989/1990; AA 4.3 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.3)
  - School of Engineering, 1988/1989; AA 4.4 (Box 18, Folder AA 4.4)
  - School of Engineering, 1990; AA 4.4 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.4)
  - School of Education, 1988; AA 4.5 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.5)
  - School of Medicine, 9/1989-12/1989; AA 4.6 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 1/1990-6/1990; AA 4.6 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.6)
  - School of Medicine, 7/1990-12/1990; AA 4.6 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.6)
  - Hoover Institution, 9/1989-12/1989; AA 4.9 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Hoover Institution, 1990; AA 4.9 (Box 19, Folder AA 4.9)
  - Hoover Board of Overseers, 9/1989-12/1989; AA 4.9.1 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.9.1)
  - Hoover Board of Overseers, 1990; AA 4.9.1 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.9.1)
  - Ctr. for the Study of Language and Info., 1983-1985; AA 4.14.1 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.14.1)
  - Ctr. for the Study of Language and Info., 1986/1987; AA 4.14.1 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.14.1)
  - Law School, 9/88-89; AA 4.15 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Law School, 1989; AA 4.15 (Box 20, Folder AA 4.15)
  - Stanford Hospital, 9/1989-12/1989; AA 4.17 (Box 21, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 1/1990-5/1990; AA 4.17 (Box 21, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 6/1990-8/1990; AA 4.17 (Box 21, Folder AA 4.17)
  - Stanford Hospital, 9/1990-12/1990; AA 4.17 (Box 21, Folder AA 4.17)
  - SU Hospital Board of Directors, 1988/1989; AA 4.17.2 (Box 21, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - SUH Nominations Committee, 1990; AA 4.17.2 (Box 22, Folder AA 4.17.2)
  - New Children's Hospital, 1979-1989; PAA 4.17.5/1 (Box 22, Folder PAA 4.17.5/1)
  - Animal Rights Issues/Facilities, 1986-1988; AA 4.17.6 (Box 22, Folder AA 4.17.6)
  - Information Resources, VP, 1982-1988; PAA 4.22.2 (Box 22, Folder PAA 4.22.2)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1983; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1984; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1985; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1986; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1987; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1988; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1989; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Awards and Prizes, Miscellaneous, 1990; AA 5 (Box 23, Folder AA 5)
  - Student Protest, 1989; ST 1 (Box 24, Folder ST 1)
  - Students Miscellaneous, 9/1989-90; ST 1 (Box 24, Folder ST 1)
  - General ASSU, 1981-1989; ST 2 (Box 24, Folder ST 2)
  - Bechtel International Center, 1980-1987; ST 3.5 (Box 24, Folder ST 3.5)
  - Black Student Union, 1983-1989; ST 3.6 (Box 24, Folder ST 3.6)
  - Public Service Center and ODN, 1989; ST 3.29 (Box 24, Folder ST 3.29)
  - Public Service Center and ODN, 1990; ST 3.29 (Box 24, Folder ST 3.29)
  - Senior Class, 1986-1989; ST 5.4 (Box 24, Folder ST 5.4)
  - Outside Organizations (five folders), 12/1989-12/1990; 0 1 (Box 25, Folder 0 1)
  - Health Effects Institute, 1981-1990; 2.1 (Box 25, Folder 2.1)
  - Consort. on Financing Higher Education, 1989/1990; 3.1 (Box 25, Folder 3.1)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1983-1990; 3.7 (Box 25, Folder 3.7)
  - Institute of Medicine (IoM), 1989/1990; 3.42 (Box 26, Folder 3.42)
  - Other Universities and Colleges, 9/1989-8/1990; 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Other Universities and Colleges, 9/1990-12/1990; 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Association of American Universities, 1985-1989; 8.7 (Box 27, Folder 8.7)
  - Association of American Universities, 1990; 8.7 (Box 27, Folder 8.7)
  - Harvard University, 1983-1990; 8.23 (Box 27, Folder 8.23)
  - Eight University Provost's Group, 1983-1989; 8.39 (Box 27, Folder 8.39)
  - Western Assoc. of Schools and Colleges, 9/1989-90; 8.52 (Box 27, Folder 8.52)
  - Inaugurations, Other Schools, 1983-1989; 8.55 (Box 27, Folder 8.55)
  - Sponsored Projects, 9/1989-90; R 1 (Box 28, Folder R 1)
  - Inst. for Res. on Women and Gender, 1983-1989; R 1.8 (Box 28, Folder R 1.8)
  - Biotechnology Conference: Follow-ups, 1982; R 2.3 (Box 28, Folder R 2.3)
  - Alumni Relations, 1982-1990; AL 1 (Box 28, Folder AL 1)
  - Alumni Association, 9/1989-90; AL 3 (Box 28, Folder AL 3)
  - Academic Council, 9/1989-90; C 1 (Box 28, Folder C 1)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 9/1989-90; C 2 (Box 28, Folder C 2)
  - Advisory Board, 9/1989-90; C 3 (Box 29, Folder C 3)
  - Steering Committee, 1987-1990; C 4.1 (Box 29, Folder C 4.1)
  - Committee on Committees, 1987-1989; C 4.2 (Box 29, Folder C 4.2)
  - Comm. on Faculty and Staff Benefits, 9/1989-8/1990; C 6.5 (Box 29, Folder C 6.5)
  - Comm. on Fac. Recruitment and Relations, 9/1989-8/1990; C 6.5.2 (Box 29, Folder C 6.5.2)
  - Committee on Public Events, 1972-1986; C 6.8 (Box 29, Folder C 6.8)
  - University Comm. on Minority Issues, 9/1989-8/1990; C 6.9.2 (Box 29, Folder C 6.9.2)
  - Commission on Invest. Responsibility, 1971-1985; C 7.7 (Box 30, Folder C 7.7)
  - Commission on Invest. Responsibility, 1986-1988; C 7.7 (Box 30, Folder C 7.7)
  - Panel on Use of Human Subjects in Res., 1973-1976; C 8.7 (Box 30, Folder C 8.7)
  - Honor Code Commission, 1979-1988; C 9.5 (Box 30, Folder C 9.5)
  - California State Government, 9/1989-8/1990; G 1.2 (Box 30, Folder G 1.2)
  - Calif. Post secondary Ed. Commission, 1985-1988; G 1.3.5 (Box 30, Folder G 1.3.5)
  - US Government Relations, 9/1989-8/1990; G 3 (Box 30, Folder G 3)
  - Federal Legislation, 9/1989-8/1990; G 3.1 (Box 30, Folder G 3.1)
  - Nat'I Aeronautics and Space Admin., 1983-1989; G 3.7.4 (Box 30, Folder G 3.7.4)
  - Department of Health, Ed. and Welfare, 1986-1987; G 3.8 (Box 30, Folder G 3.8)
  - Department of Health, Ed. and Welfare, 1988-1990; G 3.8 (Box 30, Folder G 3.8)
  - Archibald/Marsh Meeting, 1988; G 3.8 (Box 31, Folder G 3.8)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH), 1982-1989; G 3.8.2 (Box 31, Folder G 3.8.2)
  - National Science Foundation, 1988-1990; G 3.19 (Box 31, Folder G 3.19)
  - Federal Agencies, Miscellaneous, 1983-1989; G 3.29 (Box 31, Folder G 3.29)
  - Palo Alto Community Relations, 1983-1989; G 4.2 (Box 31, Folder G 4.2)
  - USSR, 9/1989-8/1990; G 5.1 (Box 31, Folder G 5.1)
  - S. Africa/Carnegie Mtg. on Ed. Reform, 31315; G 5.3 (Box 32, Folder G 5.3)
  - Other Univ. S. Africa Correspondence, 9/1989-8/1990; G 5.3 (Box 32, Folder G 5.3)
  - Board of Trustees, 1982-1988; B 1 (Box 32, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1989; B 1 (Box 32, Folder B 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1990; B 1 (Box 32, Folder B 1)
  - BoT Mtg./Min./Schedules, 1982-1989; B 13 (Box 32, Folder B 13)
  - BoT Committee on Academic Affairs, 1981-1986; B 14.3 (Box 32, Folder B 14.3)
  - BoT Finance and Devel. Committee, 1985-1988; B 14.4 (Box 32, Folder B 14.4)
  - BoT Finance and Devel. Committee, 1989-90; B 14.4 (Box 32, Folder B 14.4)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (D. Kennedy), 10/1979-12/1979 (Box 33)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (D. Kennedy), 1/80-12/1980 (Box 33)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (A. Hastorf), 1/1981-9/1981 (Box 33)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (A. Hastorf), 10/1981-12/1981 (Box 34)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (A. Hastorf), 1982 (Box 34)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (A. Hastorf), 1983 (Box 34)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (A. Hastorf), 1/1984-8/1984 (Box 35)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (J. Rosse), 9/1984-12/1984 (Box 35)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (J. Rosse), 1985 (Box 35)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (J. Rosse), 1986 (Box 36)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (J. Rosse), 1987 (Box 36)
  - Vice President and Provost Chrons (J. Rosse), 1988 (Box 37)
  - President Chrons (D. Kennedy), 1988 (Box 38)
  - President Chrons (D. Kennedy), 1989 (Box 39)
  - President Chrons (D. Kennedy), 1990 (Box 40)
  - Provost's Office Mail Summaries (1 of 3), 1981; 1 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Provost's Office Mail Summaries (2 of 3), 1981; 2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Provost's Office Mail Summaries (3 of 3), 1981; 3 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Mail Summaries (1 of 3), 1982; 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Mail Summaries (2 of 3), 1982; 5 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Mail Summaries (3 of 3), 1982; 6 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - DAPER, 1985/1986; 7 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Trustee Development, 8 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Sub-committee (two folders), 1983-85; 9 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Rhinelander-Stockdale, 1985/1986; 10 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Physical Therapy, 30742; 40862 (Box 41, Folder 40862)
  - Provost's Files Commencement (five folders), 1982/83, 1985, 1987/88; 40548 (Box 42, Folder 40548)
  - Jewish Studies, 1982; 6 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Martin Luther King Papers, 1985/1986; 7 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Luce Foundation, 1987/88; 8 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Meier-Lodato Proposal, 31424; 9 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Monterey Institute, 31301; 10 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Islamic Studies, 31110; 11 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Academic Space-Department of Pharmacology, 31887; 12 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - A Majors Event, 30446; 13 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Melton Foundation, 31434; 14 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - National Center for Language, 15 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Pedagogy, 31586; 16 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Washington D.C. Campus Budget, 31901; 17 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Western Culture Task Force, 1986/1987; 18 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Student/Faculty Grievances on Academic Matters, 26360; 19 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Sexual Harassment on Campus, 30236; 20 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Senior Survey, 30357; 21 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Melton Foundation, 30441; 22 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Compensation Proposal (Fall 1984), 1985/1986; 23 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Facilities Project Management Status Report, 1986; 24 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Visiting Scholar-Madame Sadat, 31553; 25 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Overseas Studies Program, 31670; 26 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stanford in Vienna, 31885; 27 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Termination of Permanent Resident, 28 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Status (Kazuhiko Tatemoto), 31940; 29 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Ryan Lab Site, 31979; 30 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Green Folder Group, 1985-88; 31 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Near West Campus (three folders), 1986; 32 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Near West Campus (1 of 3), 1987; 33 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Near West Campus (2 of 3), 1987; 34 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Near West Campus (3 of 3), 1987; 35 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - President's Files Alliance for Philanthropy, 1986; 1 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - American Journal of Physiology, 1976; 2 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - American Medical Association, 3 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Congress on Peer Review, 1986-88; 4 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Ano Nuevo Interpretative Association, 1987/88; 5 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Bohemian Grove/Club, 1986-91; 6 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Bay Area Economic Forum, 1986-91; 7 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Council on Competitiveness (1 of 2), 1988-92; 8 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Council on Competitiveness (2 of 2), 1988-92; 9 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Economics of National Security, 10 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Project, 1986-88; 11 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Friends of ICIPE, 1986; 12 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Long Range Planning Interviews, 1987-89; 13 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Long Range Planning Questionnaire, 1987-88; 14 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Long Range Planning Group, 1986-87; 15 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Long Range Planning External, 1986-87; 16 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Universities Research Association, 1984-89; 17 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Winter Conference on Brain, 18 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Research-WCBR, 1988; 19 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Stanford in the Second Century, 1990; 20 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Americans for Generational, 21 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Equity (AGE), 1988; 22 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Teach II, 1991; 23 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Teach II Letters from Faculty, 24 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Teach II Background Materials, 25 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence re Teach I, 1991; 26 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - (APC) Action Plans for Change, 1 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Steering Committee (1 of 2), 1990; 2 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee (2 of 2), 1990; 3 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Reorganization (two folders), 1989-91; 4 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - BoT Reorganization, 1990; 5 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - APC Libraries Team Management Liaison Group, 6 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - APC Action Teams (Summaries of reports), 7 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - APC Facilities, 8 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - APC-HRO, 9 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - APC Vision Team, 10 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Master Copy: APC HRO Document, 11 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - APC Action Teams (Charges Included), 1990; 12 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - APC Student Services, 13 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Action Plan for Change Faculty Interviews, 14 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - APC Objectives/Publicity Flyers/General Info., 15 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - APC Studies, 16 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - APC Steering Committee, 17 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Action Plan for Change, 18 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Advance Committee of the Directorate for Science and Engineering Education of the Nat'l Science Foundation, 1990; 1 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1976-91; 2 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - BAJPAI, 3 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 1988-92; 4 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - The California Institute, 1992; 5 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - California Times Public, Affairs Radio; 6 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - California Tomorrow, 1979-91; 7 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Coalition for National Service, 1986-90; 8 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Food and Drug Law Institute, 1979-90; 9 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Foundation on Biomedical Research, 1988-92; 10 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Friends of the Nat'I Library of Medicine, 1989-92; 11 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Global Tomorrow Coalition, 1989-91; 12 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Nat'l Assn. for Biomedical Research and Fdn. for Biomedical Research, 1989; 13 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Nat'l Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1989/1990; 14 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Nat'I Institute Against Prejudice and Violence, 1988; 15 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Leon Sullivan, 1988; 16 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Appointment Calendars (Nine Years), 1980-1988; 17 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - A-H Recommendations (Box 46)
  - F-N Recommendations (Box 47)
  - M-Z Recommendations (Box 48)
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1993-068
  - BOT Agendas and Pre-Agendas, 9/1989-8/1990; B 13.3 (Box 1, Folder B 13.3)
  - Students on Trustee Committees, 1983-89; B 14.2.3 (Box 1, Folder B 14.2.3)
  - BOT Committee on Academic Affairs, 1987-90; B 14.3 (Box 1, Folder B 14.3)
  - BOT Investment Committee, 1988-89; B 14.5 (Box 1, Folder B 14.5)
  - Committee on Nominations, 9/1989-90; B 14.7 (Box 1, Folder B 14.7)
  - ASSU Committee on Nominations, 1987-89; ST 2.7 (Box 1, Folder ST 2.7)
  - ASSU Senate, 1982-89; ST 2.10 (Box 1, Folder ST 2.10)
  - Stanford Band (2 Folders), 1983-85; ST 3.4 (Box 1, Folder ST 3.4)
  - Stanford Band, 1986-87; ST 3.4 (Box 1, Folder ST 3.4)
  - Stanford Misc. Stanfordania, 1988-91; AD 1 (Box 1, Folder AD 1)
  - Centennial (Jan.-June) 3 Folders, 1991; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial (July-Sept.), 1991; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Centennial (Oct.-Dec.), 1991; AD 1.3 (Box 1, Folder AD 1.3)
  - Stanford Statistics (File sent to Public Affairs), 1988-91; AD 1.5 (Box 2, Folder AD 1.5)
  - Administrative Council, 1990-91; AD 4.12 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.12)
  - Academic Secretary, 1987-89; AD 4.14 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.14)
  - General Counsel, 1988-91; AD 4.19 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.19)
  - Correspondence, 1990-91; AD 4.20 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20)
  - Condolence Letters, 1990-91; AD 4.20.2 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.2)
  - Congratulations Letters, 1991; AD 4.20.3 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.3)
  - Complaints, 1991; AD 4.20.7 (Box 2, Folder AD 4.20.7)
  - Campus Disruptions, 1985-89; AD 7.2 (Box 2, Folder AD 7.2)
  - Admissions Office, 1991; AD 8.1 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.1)
  - Admissions Cases, 1991; AD 8.1.2 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.1.2)
  - Dean of Student Affairs (Jan.-May) 2 Folders, 1991; AD 8.8 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.8)
  - Dean of Student Affairs (June-Aug.), 1991; AD 8.8 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.8)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emerti 2 Folders, 1984-90; AD 8.18 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emerti, 1991; AD 8.18 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1988-91; AD 8.18 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.18)
  - Student Housing, 1990-91; AD 8.18.11 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Domestic Partners, 1990-91; AD 8.18.11 (Box 2, Folder AD 8.18.11)
  - Residential Education, 1988-91; AD 8.18.13 (Box 3, Folder AD 8.18.13)
  - Chicano Affairs, 1988-91; AD 9.2 (Box 3, Folder AD 9.2)
  - Demmert/Native American Affairs, 1991; AD 9.3 (Box 3, Folder AD 9.3)
  - Staff Affirmative Action Program, 1990; AD 9.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 9.6)
  - Employment Injuries and Requests, 1991; AD 10.1 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.1)
  - Management Development Program, 1988-90; AD 10.2 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.2)
  - Human Resources Council, 1988-91; AD 10.4 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.4)
  - United Stanford Employees, 1988-91; AD 10.7.8 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.7.8)
  - Faculty and Staff Benefits, 1991; AD 10.8.9 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.9)
  - Grievance Procedures, 1989-91; AD 10.8.10 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.10)
  - Grievance Cases, 1988-90; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.10/1)
  - Grievance Cases, Possible, 1988-91; AD 10.8.10/2 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.10/2)
  - Retirement, 1990-91; AD 10.8.17 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.17)
  - TIAA/CREF, 1988-91; AD 10.8.17/3 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.17/3)
  - Salaries, 1989-91; AD 10.8.19 (Box 3, Folder AD 10.8.19)
  - Service Operations, 1988-91; AD 11.4 (Box 3, Folder AD 11.4)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, 1987-91; AD 11.6 (Box 3, Folder AD 11.6)
  - Commencement, 1988-91; AD 11.7.2 (Box 3, Folder AD 11.7.2)
  - Commencement Speakers, 1988-90; AD 11.7.2/1 (Box 3, Folder AD 11.7.2/1)
  - Publication Services/Communications, 1988-91; AD 11.8 (Box 3, Folder AD 11.8)
  - Stanford Press, 1991; AD 11.8.9 (Box 4, Folder AD 11.8.9)
  - Surveys, Studies and Questionnaires, 1991; AD 11.8.10 (Box 4, Folder AD 11.8.10)
  - Campus Publications, Misc., 1988-91; AD 11.8.11 (Box 4, Folder AD 11.8.11)
  - V.P for Business and Finance, 1989-90; AD 12.2.1. (Box 4, Folder AD 12.2.1.)
  - Vice President for Finance, 1989-91; AD 12.2/2 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.2/2)
  - Vice President for Human Resources, 1989-91; AD 12.2/3 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.2/3)
  - Treasurer, 1991; AD 12.3 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.3)
  - Stanford Investment Management Office, 1988-91; AD 12.3.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.3.1)
  - Auditing, 1991; AD 12.4 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.4)
  - Budget (Feb., Nov. and Dec.) 3 Folders, 1990; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budget (Jan.-March), 1991; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Budget (Apr.-May), 1991; AD 12.5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5)
  - Office of Management and Budget, 1989-90; AD 12.5.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.5.1)
  - Health and Safety 3 Folders, 6/1991-11/1989; AD 12.8.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Health and Safety, 10/1989-4/1989; AD 12.8.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Health and Safety, 3/1989-1/1989; AD 12.8.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.8.1)
  - Office of Development (OOD), 1991; AD 12.10.1 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.1)
  - OOD (B), 1982-90; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 4, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (C), 1986-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (G), 1987-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (H), 1986-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (J), 1987-1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (L), 1987-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (M), 1986-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (P), 1986-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (S), 1986-1991; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - OOD (W), 1988-91; AD 12.10.3/5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5)
  - Annenberg, Walter H., 1983-90; AD 12.10.3/5-4 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-4)
  - Chevron Oil, 1982-91; AD 12.10.3/5-5 (Box 5, Folder AD 12.10.3/5-5)